Thanks for sharing the table with me. To think all the other patrons are actually avoiding me. Hmph. I'll remember this
Merci de vous joindre à moi. Les autres clients m'évitent comme la peste. Hmph, ils ne perdent rien pour attendre.
Seriously... They care that much about my lineage? Even if I were out for vengeance, they'd have to wait their turn
Bon sang... Mon ascendance familiale leur importe tant que cela ? Admettons que je veuille me venger, ces gens devront sagement attendre leur tour.
The Gunnhildr clan, the Ragnvindr clan, and the Lawrence clan are the three most prominent families in Mondstadt's history
Les clans Gunnhildr, Ragnvindr et Lawrence sont les trois plus illustres familles de l'histoire de Mondstadt.
Among them, the Lawrence clan became blinded by their desires, plunging Mondstadt into a dark era under the aristocracy's oppression
Aveuglé par son ambition, le clan Lawrence plongea Mondstadt dans l'ère sombre de la tyrannie aristocratique.
In time, Lady Vennessa overthrew the aristocracy and established the Knights of Favonius while the Lawrence clan quickly fell into obscurity
À cette époque, dame Vennessa renversa l'aristocratie et fonda l'Ordre de Favonius, tandis que le clan Lawrence tomba dans l'oubli.
Over the next thousand years, their flame of vengeance continued to flicker and burn, but never again did it ignite into a blaze
Pendant le millénaire qui suivit, le feu de la vengeance continuait de l'animer, mais il ne fut jamais assez fort pour s'embraser.
Perhaps the finishing blow to the Lawrence clan was...
Le coup de grâce pour le clan Lawrence était
She who is known as the "Spindrift Knight," most gifted descendant of the Lawrence clan, Eula, joining the Knights of Favonius
de voir Eula, le « Chevalier aux Embruns » et sa plus remarquable descendante, rejoindre l'Ordre de Favonius.
Although the word "vengeance" is always upon her lips, she has proved time and again that she is a kindhearted and honorable ally
Bien qu'elle parle souvent de vengeance, Eula a su prouver à maintes reprises qu'elle était une alliée honorable au grand cœur.
Hey, when a noblewoman is speaking, you are to lower your drink and look her directly in the eyes. You really ought to learn some proper etiquette...
Hé ! Quand une noble vous parle, il faut baisser son verre et la regarder droit dans les yeux. Allez donc prendre des cours d'étiquette...
Achoo! Oh, I bet it's that Gunnhildr girl talking about me behind my back again...
Atchoum ! Je parie que la fille des Gunnhildr est encore en train de parler derrière mon dos...
Hmph! Mark my words... vengeance will be mine!
Hmph ! Retenez mes mots : la vengeance sera mienne !